Finding Aid for the Motion Picture Advertising Ephemera PASC.0160
UCLA Library Special Collections
Motion picture advertising ephemera
circa 1915- circa 1995
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0160
10.5 Linear Feet (21 boxes)
The collection consists of publicity-related ephemera for American motion pictures.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328243606533
History
The history for this collection is not available at this time.
Scope and Content
Collection consists mostly of programs and other publicity-related ephemera associated with American motion pictures. Includes numerous fold-out programs, fold-out posters, souvenir books, and souvenir programs. Also includes other ephemera such as bumper stickers, pop-up and stand-up displays, Variety advertising supplements, calendars, and event invitations. Material is predominately English.
Programs.; Souvenir programs.; Advertisements.; Advertising -- Motion pictures.
- ABYSS, THE,., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographies and production information booklets encased in an illustrated cardboard box.
- ACTORS FUND OF AMERICA,., 1922 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Souvenir program for Second Annual Pacific Coast Benefit Actors Fund of America. Hollywood Bowl, October 7, 1922.
- AGONY AND THE ECSTASY, THE,., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes and ceiling of the Sistine Chapel, story summary, information about players, creators, and artists.
- ALL THE PRESIDENT'S MEN,., no date (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text "production notes."
- AMERICAN IN PARIS, AN,., no date (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Souvenir programme book. Invitational Hollywood premiere at the Egyptian Theatre.
- ANDROMEDA STRAIN, THE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Uniquely shaped fold-out souvenir program.
- ANNIE,., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and assorted brief reviews.
- ANTIQUES,., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Fold-out programme. Story summary in English, French, and German and director's filmography.
- APOCALYPSE NOW,., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Souvenir programme. Includes production information, credits, and information about cast and crew.
- AVENTURE EST AU COIN DE LA RUE, L',., no date (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Fold-out programme. Includes a collage of pictures of scenes and story summary in French.
- BAL DU MOULIN ROUGE DE PARIS,., no date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Fold-out programme. French and English.
- BALANCE, THE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, and commentary by Bozena Janicka in English, French and German.
- BARRY LYNDON,., no date (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Pictorial souvenir program.
- BATTLEGROUND,., no date (Box 4, Folder 8)
  2 items: Souvenir programme and invitation to preview premiere.
- BEAST WITHIN, THE,., 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  2 pins and 1 bumper sticker.
- BEFORE THE DAY BREAKS,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- BEGUILED, THE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Fold-out programme includes cast, credits and production notes.
- BEING THERE,., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Fold-out programme.
- BELLBOY, THE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Fold-out poster.
- BELLE ET LA BETE, LA,., no date (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Souvenir programme book, fragile. Text in French. B/W pictures of scenes and principal players.
- BEN-HUR,., no date (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, and information about production and creative talents.
- BENNY GOODMAN STORY, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text "About the Benny Goodman Story." Two page listing of Music: title, composer, and performer.
- BEST WHOREHOUSE IN TEXAS, THE,., no date (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Fold-out programme. Includes cast and credit information.
- BEST YEARS OF OUR LIVES, THE,., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. Includes text "the idea" and the "story of the film."
- BIBLE, THE,., no date (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Souvenir book. Dino De Laurentiis Production. Includes color and b/w pictures of scenes, credits, and production information.
- BIG ARRANGEMENT,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in English, French, and German.
- BIG DEAL,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, story summary in English, French and German, and director's filmography.
- BIG FIX, THE,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of Richard Dreyfuss.
- BILOXI BLUES,., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  3 post cards from the character Eugene.
- BINGO LONG TRAVELING ALL-STARS & MOTOR KINGS, THE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes.
- BIRDY,., no date (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Pictorial souvenir book.
- BIRTH OF A NATION,., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Souvenir programme published by EPOCH Producing Corporation.
- BLADE RUNNER,., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Souvenir magazine. Includes table of contents, photos of scenes, interviews, illustrations and more.
- BLUE DENIM,., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Variety article and ad campaign information.
- BLUE THUNDER,., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  One page programme.
- BOUND FOR GLORY,., no date (Box 1, Folder 18)
- BREAKFAST AT TIFFANY'S,., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  Pamphlet like ad from Variety Oct. 17, 1961.
- BREWSTER MCCLOUD,., no date (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Fold-out programme. Brief summaries of individual actors and their character.
- BRIGHTON BEACH MEMOIRS,., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Pocket size photo album with pictures and captions.
- BRINK'S JOB, THE,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  One page programme. Includes illustration characters waist deep in paper money.
- BRUNET WILL CALL, A,., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- BUCK ROGERS,., no date (Box 3, Folder 49)
- BUFFY THE VAMPIRE SLAYER,., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Ad gimmick- Hemery High School Yearbook 1992.
- BUTTERFLY'S SEASON,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- CABARET,., no date (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos from scenes, story synopsis, and brief accounts of major creative talent.
- CABOBLANCO,., no date (Box 10, Folder 2)
  2 items- Oversize advertising supplements to Variety. Fold out ad, and 6 page book like illustrations of lead characters.
- CALIFORNIA SUITE,., no date (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Fold-out programme in the shape of a suitcase. Includes cast and credit information.
- CAMELOT,., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes and text- about various aspects of the film- production, characters, artifacts, costumes, sets, and more.
- CAMOUFLAGE,., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, story summary in English, French, and German and director's filmography.
- CAPRICORN ONE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CARAVANS,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of characters in battle.
- CAST A GIANT SHADOW,., no date (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Fold-out programme. Includes brief summary about the story and major cast.
- CBS THEATRICAL FILMS,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  2 items identical, different size. Production preview
- CHALLENGING, THE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story synopsis.
- CHAPLIN,., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Souvenir book. - rbc films catalog of ten Chaplin feature films. Includes photos of scenes and commentary.
- CHASSEUR DE CHEZ MAXIM'S, LE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in French, Spanish, English, and German.
- CHEAP DETECTIVE, THE,., no date (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Fold-out pop ad.
- CHORUS LINE,., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Fold-out ad "for your consideration".
- CINE ESPANOL,., no date (Box 13)
  Cine Espanol Film Festival Spain. Materials from 1973, 1974, 1975.
- CIRCUS WORLD,., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. Includes picture of scenes, story summary, information about production and creative talents.
- CLEOPATRA,., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary and information about Cleoparta and creative talent.
- CLUE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Ad gimmick with clue wheel.
- COCK EYED WORLD, THE,., no date (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Souvenir book from Grauman's Chinese. Includes captioned pictures of scenes.
- COCK EYED WORLD, THE,., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Elaborate souvenir program for the western premiere September 24, 1929.
- COLUMBIA,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Advertising supplement to Variety. Fold-out preview of production releases. Sample posters.
- CONCORDE-AIRPORT '79, THE,., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of concorde and missile.
- COVERED WAGON, THE,., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. "Prepared to present the public interesting facts in connection with the production." Includes pictures of players.
- COWBOY IN AFRICA,., no date (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Publicity manual prepared for Vantors Films Limited by Frank L. Law, unit publicity director. Includes table of contents and b/w photos of scenes.
- CRAZY PEOPLE,., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Pin that says- Crazy People it takes ton to know one!
- CREEPSHOW,., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Fold-out pop-up counter display and 3x5 card.
- CROMWELL,., no date (Box 15, Folder 28)
  Souvenir book. Includes story synopsis, and information about creative talents.
- CROSS OF IRON,., no date (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Fold-out programme. Includes production notes text.
- CTD,., no date (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story summary in English, French and German and pictures from scenes.
- CUBA,., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- DAGNY,., no date (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and a commentary by Wojciech Wierzewski.
- DANCING HAWK, THE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- DANGER,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- DEAD OF SUMMER,., no date (Box 2, Folder 50)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in English and French. Programme folds out into a poster.
- DEER HUNTER, THE,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- DEER HUNTER, THE,., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Souvenir book. Primarily picture of scenes.
- DIFFERENT,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, director's filmography, and story summary in English, French, German.
- DIME WITH A HALO,., no date (Box 3, Folder 38)
- DOCTOR DOLITTLE,., no date (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, credits, information about creative talents and production.
- DOCTOR JUDYM,., no date (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, and story summary in English, French and German.
- DOCTOR ZHIVAGO,., no date (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, information on creative talent, and credits.
- DOLL, THE (LA POUPEE),., no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Souvenir book. Includes text in French and English about players and director.
- DOOM, THE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 58)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, and story summary in English, French, and German.
- DRACULA,., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of Dracula and a woman.
- DUNE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 48)
- E.T. THE EXTRA-TERRESTRIAL,., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  One page programme. Includes graphic of finger touch.
- EARLY SPRING DAYS, THE,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes and story summary in English, French, and German.
- EARTHQUAKE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Fold-out programme. Includes thumb nail headshots of cast and production notes.
- EDWARD SCISSORHANDS,., 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Unique counter display fold-out pop-up.
- EIGHT HUNDRED HEROES,., no date (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Pamphlet type program. Programme in Chinese and English. Includes brief summary of story and pictures of scenes.
- EL CID,., no date (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and text about story, production and creative talent.
- ENCINO MAN,., no date (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Ad gimmick
- END OF THE HOLIDAY, THE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Fold-out programme. Includes collage of pictures from scenes and story summary in Russian, English, French, and German.
- ENTANGLED FEELINGS,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- EROTIC ADVENTURES OF ZORRO, THE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 60)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story summary and pictures of scenes.
- EVERY WHICH WAY BUT LOOSE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 16)
  One-page programme. Includes illustrations of characters.
- FABULOUS FILM CALENDAR, THE,., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  1978 calendar compiled by LaVerne Owens, cover design by Robin Netzer, art production by Michael Mekeel. Trivia and illustrations specific to the film industry.
- FACE OF FU MANCHU, THE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Fold-out ad.
- FALL OF THE ROMAN EMPIRE, THE,., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, and information about players and creators.
- FALLEN LEAVES,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story summary in English, French and German.
- FAMILY, THE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Fold out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, and story summary in English, French, and German.
- FANTASIA,., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Souvenir programme book. Includes photos of creators and illustrations from the film. Credits and commentary about the music.
- FAR FROM THE MADDENING CROWD,., no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Souvenir book. Predominately pictorial.
- FAREWELL TO ARMS, A,., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Souvenir book. Includes text- about the book, about the film, about the cast.
- FASCINATION,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Fold out-programme. Includes pictures from scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- FEAR, THE,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- FILM TEST, THE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in English, French, and German, and directors' filmographies in English.
- FOR THE BOYS,., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- FOR THE LOVE OF BENJI,., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of and information about the production.
- FORCE 10 FORM NAVARONE,., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- FOUL PLAY,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  "Film Polski presents." Fold out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- FRANKFURT COMMUNICATIONS,., no date (Box 12, Folder 18)
  A division of Kenyon & Eckhardt Advertising. Supplement to Variety. Folds out to a poster of a retrospective view of posters.
- FRENCH CONNECTION II,., no date (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Handmade scrap book. Includes a limited number of photos of lobby displays and marquees, and Japanese newspaper clippings.
- FRENZY,., no date (Box 3, Folder 31)
- FROM NOWHERE TO NOWHERE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 44)
- FRONT, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Fold-out programme. Includes illustration of Woody Allen profile.
- FUNNY GIRL,., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. Includes TOC, b/w and color pictures, information about production and creative talents
- GAMBLERS,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Fold-out programme. Includes small pictures of face scenes and story summary in English, French and German.
- GLORY,., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- GODFATHER PART II, THE,., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Fold-out programme. Includes the Godfather Family Tree.
- GODFATHER, THE,., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, and information about production and creative talents.
- GOLDCREST FILMS & TELEVISION LTD,., no date (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Booklet of 7 sample posters.
- GOLDEN GIRL,., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  Ad from Box-office publication- Feb. 26, 1979.
- GONE WITH THE WIND,., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Souvenir programme book for the Tara Ball 10/3/67, and Loew's Grand Theatre 10/4/67- Atlanta, Georgia.
- GORGON CASE, THE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French and German, and director's filmography.
- GORILLAS IN THE MIST THE ADVENTURE OF DIANE FOSSEY,., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- GRAND CANYON,., 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Grauman's Hollywood Egyptian Theatre,., no date (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Souvenir album book for the dedication of the Egyptian Theatre
- GRAY LADY DOWN,., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes.
- GREASE,., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Unique fold-out invitation to Mann's Chinese Theatre, June 4.
- GREASE,., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- GREAT RACE, THE,., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. Includes information about production, creators, and players.
- GREATEST STORY EVER TOLD, THE,., no date (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Predominantly pictorial.
- GREYSTOKE THE LEGEND OF TARZAN LORD OF THE APES,., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- HALF A SIXPENCE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 45)
  Pamphlet type programme. Includes pictures from scenes and limited information on creators and lead player.
- HALLELUJAH TRAIL, THE,., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, and brief information about the players, the story, and production.
- HALLELUJAH!,., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Souvenir book, and programs- 3 items. Larger pamphlet includes text "the story of Hallelujah" and pictures of cast and scenes. Smaller fold out from Fox Palace, LA. Smaller- fold out programme.
- HAWAII,., no date (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Souvenir book- hard cover. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary, and production information.
- HEAVEN'S GATE,., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- HEROES,., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- HINDENBURG,., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Fold-out programme. Includes an insert with fact information about the Hindenburg. Small card stapled in lower rt corner "Attention Viewing Press".
- HISTORY OF THE WORLD PART I,., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Fold-out programme. Includes small pictures of scenes and cast.
- HOLE IN THE HEAD, A,., no date (Box 2, Folder 61)
  Ad from an unknown publication.
- HOME ALONE,., 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Unique press kit. Large cardboard suitcase. Includes ten 8x10 b/w stills.
- HOME FOR THE HOLIDAYS,., 1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Fold-out programme includes cast and credit listing.
- HOOK,., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- HOPE, BOB (ON THE ROAD WITH BOB HOPE),., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Souvenir brochure by Popular Programs, Inc. Includes b/w pictures and promotional biographical information.
- HOPSCOTCH,., no date (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Fold-out programme. Includes summary about the production.
- HORSE SOLDIERS, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 43)
  2 items: fold out programme that opens to a poster, Variety ad (no date).
- HOT ROCK, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 13)
  One page programme. Includes miscellaneous production information.
- HOUR AFTER HOUR,., no date (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Fold-out program. Includes pictures from scenes, and story summary in English, French and German.
- HOUSE CALLS,., no date (Box 1, Folder 10)
- HOW THE WEST WAS WON,., no date (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes color and b/w photos-some are captioned story synopsis, information about production and creative talents, and credits.
- HUSBANDS,., no date (Box 7, Folder 12)
- I AM THE KILLER,., no date (Box 2, Folder 31)
- IN THE HEIGHT OF SUMMER,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- INDIANA JONES AND THE TEMPLE OF DOOM,., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Pictorial souvenir book. Includes captions with pictures.
- INVASION OF THE BODY SNATCHERS,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- IRON MASK, THE,., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Souvenir book published by the Longacre Press.
- ISADORA,., no date (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Special press kit. Includes b/w photos, credits, story synopsis, and information about creative talent.
- ISLAND OF DR. MOREAU, THE,., no date (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and production information.
- IT'S A MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD WORLD,., no date (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Souvenir book. Subtitle-the story of the making of the motion picture. Includes cast credit, some cast photos, and some production information.
- J&M FILM SALES LTD,., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Fold-out production preview. Samples of posters.
- JAROS,., no date (Box 2, Folder 3)
  2 items- Larger fold out programme includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French and German. Smaller fold out programme includes pictures of scenes and Polish text.
- JAWS,., no date (Box 1, Folder 46)
  3 items- fold out programme, text Facts About Sharks, and over size fold-out listing of excerpts of reviews.
- JAWS 2,., no date (Box 3, Folder 12)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of Jaws and water-skier.
- JEALOUSY AND MEDICINE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and text in French and German.
- JERK, THE,., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  One page programme. Includes picture of Steve Martin.
- JOHN AND MARY,., no date (Box 3, Folder 9)
  One page programme. Includes production information.
- JOHN BROWN'S BODY,., no date (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Souvenir programme book published by Popular Programs. Includes information about creators and main players, including limited pictorial filmography of players.
- JUMPIN' JACK FLASH,., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Fold-out calendar.
- KARINO,., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, and story summary in English, French, German, and Russian.
- KHARTOUM,., no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Souvenir book, 2 items. Both primarily pictorial.
- KILL THAT LOVE,., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- KING CASMIR THE GREAT,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes and story summary in English, French and German.
- KING OF KINGS,., no date (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Souvenir book. Fragile.
- KING RALPH,., no date (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and satirical commentary.
- KING RALPH,., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  3 items; commemorative plastic plate, coin, and fold-out invitation to attend the coronation of that plays music when opened.
- KING SOLSOMON'S MINES,., no date (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Preview program. 3 items- program, invitation, and fold-out map/production information pamphlet.
- KNIGHTS OF THE ROUND TABLE,., no date (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Souvenir book. Text includes- the legend, the story, the production, how cinemascope works.
- KRAKATOA EAST OF JAVA,., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and information on players and creators.
- LADY CAROLINE LAMB,., no date (Box 2, Folder 59)
  Fold out programme. Includes story summary.
- LADY OF THE PAVEMENTS,., no date (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Souvenir book copied and bound in 1977. Includes b/w pictures of scenes and story summary.
- LAND OF PROMISES (ZIEMIA OBIECANA),., no date (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and commentary by Boleslaw Michalek in Russian, English, and French.
- LAST EMBRACE,., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  2 fold-out ads duplicate information, different size.
- LAST TEMPTATION OF CHRIST, THE,., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  4 items encased together- souvenir book, original and photo copy of text (making of.), and Hollywood Foreign Press interview with Barbara Hershey.
- LAWRENCE OF ARABIA,., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Souvenir book, 2 items. Larger item published by Richard Davis. Both include photos of scenes, and information about creative talents.